songonlyrics.com 2011-03-26

# Privacy Policy | Song Lyrics-Music Lyrics-Newest Lyrics With Video

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors to SongOnLyrics.com is important to us. At  
visit SongOnLyrics.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit SongOnLyrics.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.  
We will NEVER trade your personal information!We do not collect personal information.we just collect:  
Log Files  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on SongOnLyrics.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).  
Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor, use DART cookies. These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Newest Song Lyrics Archive-New Music Lyrics with Video.All lyrics are property and copyright of their owners. All lyrics provided for educational purposes only.
